从今往后我会变成什么样？
不久后，我就不再去考虑这件事了
也许我已经...
忘记如何去思考了
不会有任何改变
这个只属于我的世界
每天都在持续着
但我并不孤单
这样一点也不会让我觉得困扰
启动了应用
2539 天前
无消息
I could never find the
right way to tell you
Have you noticed I've been gone
Cause I left behind the
home that you made me
But I will carry it along
And it's a long way forward
So trust in me
I'll give them shelter
like you've done for me
And I know, I'm not alone
You'll be watching over us
Until you're gone
When I'm older I'll
be silent beside you
I know words won't be enough
And they won't need to
know the names on our faces
But they will carry on for us
And it's a long way forward
So trust in me
I'll give them shelter
like you've done for me
And I know, I'm not alone
You'll be watching over us
Until you're gone
And it's a long way forward
So trust in me
I'll give them shelter
like you've done for me
And I know, I'm not alone
You'll be watching over us
Until
即便那些记忆会令我难过
我必须前进，相信未来
即便我意识到自己的寂寞
即将失去所有希望
那些记忆让我变得更加坚强
因为有你
我不是孤身一人
谢谢你
原作  Porter Robinson
音乐  Porter Robinson / Madeon
三泽纱千香  饰  凛
故事板・监督  赤井俊文
角色设计・美术指导  河野惠美
美术  竹田悠介
动画制作  A-1 Pictures